#### Contact

6361563076 (Mobile) pranavms13@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pranavms13 (LinkedIn) pranavms.ml (Personal)

### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
MERN Stack
Android Development

### Languages

Tamil (Elementary)
Kannada (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) Python

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4

C++ Course

Machine Learning

JavaScript

# Pranav M S

#### Student

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

## Summary

I grew up in Bangalore, India.

Currently pursuing Computer Science Engineering in K S Institute of Technology. Deeply Interested in Developing applications. I started coding at the age of 10. Started many hobby projects and later worked as a Lead Developer for a Proof-Of-Work Based Cryptocurrency "ReCoal" at the age of 17.

My interests also include Web Development, Mobile App Development, IoT Based Automation, CyberSecurity Application Development.

# Experience

Bengaluru South Education and Social Transformation Web Developer January 2020 - Present (6 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

### Kaggle

Competition Contributer
October 2019 - Present (9 months)

#### Verzeo

ML Developer July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Completed Internship at Verzeo.

### Education

KS Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science  $\cdot$  (2018 - 2022)